Brickleberry
Forget video games and stop all junk food.
Write idiot, I want a hamburger.
Can you repeat?
I said I want a hamburger.
Thank you, next window.
Do you know what is this?
The devil's prick.
No
This is Brickleberry.
Welcome to Brickleberry.
Brickleberry
Here you come to enjoy nature.
Enjoy children, it is all nature in its splendor.
Respecting animals.
Hey, I found the chocolates you like.
They're all a little crazy around here.
Uh!
That pipe moves.
Ah! It’s a snake.
Why the phone posts have hairs?
They are trees, what a pain!
Fuck! There is a mailbox.
It is an owl, blows bagpipes.
Guide for a Preventive Driving
Safe driving.
My mother !, Wait, you are alive I’ll ask for help.
Either nature isn’t respected.
Oh! What the hell!
Haha, fuck nature.
This will enchant you.
Surprise!
The boy is starving.
Don’t say anything about the amputee. Do not say anything about the amputee.
He loves talking to a boy scout limb.
And we do not respect people either.
Great, this is uncomfortable.
The ones who are old, have charm, are faithful and can remove their teeth.
Quiet, let Parkinson work..
I cann’t fit anything else.
I think it will fit you.
Only you can prevent...
Fire!
Quiet! I'm going to remove the flames.
I love it! And you?
¡For Brickelberry!
Multimedia Technologies
Group 7